Hello there!
Good morning, Boxo! Hello there!
Hey, good morning, Lammis!
Karyos, Gorth, morning!
Thanks for keeping watch again today!
Sure!
Nothing beats a sweet tea
at the end of a night shift!
I look forward to serving you again!
Welp, I died and was reborn
as a venting machine.
A pretty bizarre situation
to find oneself in.
Despite the weirdness of it all, I've
still found ways to enjoy my new life.
On the outside, I'm just a big metal box,
but inside, I've still got a human soul.
In this new world of wonders,
I travel to and fro on the back
of my super strong partner,
Lamas.
The name's Boxo. Hello there!
That means yes, by the way.
Wow, summer already! Hello there!
Yeah, I'm sure does fly, huh? Oh, right.
There's a sky here with changing weather,
and the seasons change too, like on Earth.
So I forget we're in a
dungeon with multiple strata.
Once it really heats up, I'll
start selling ice cream! Boxo!
Oh, hey there, Mishuel.
I stand before you with a humble request.
By your face, it seems serious.
Yes, it is quite serious.
I have given it careful consideration.
Dear Boxo, your steel body
houses a kind and noble heart.
Your defense is top tier and
you can even raise the dead.
You are a magical item, but nonetheless,
I am totally enamored with you.
Did he say enamored?
And so, Boxo, I ask that as of today,
you grant me leave to call you master.
You mean enamored in like
a platonic way, right?
Is that a no?
Michelle is an expert hunter, no question.
But his social skills suck.
Still, that confession took
a whole lot of courage.
I gotta be mature about this. Hello there!
So that means you accept?
Oh, thank you, Master Boxo!
You won't regret it!
Um, we're just hugging his friends, right?
Right? Just friends?
Somebody's got themselves
an apprentice now.
Congrats, Boxo.
Big milestone.
Now wait just a minute!
I've got nothing to teach an apprentice!
What do I do?
All right, then, Master
Boxo, first things first.
It is time for a sponge bath.
Well, Boxo's sponge baths are my
responsibility, so you don't need to bother.
Oh, I see.
I didn't mean to step on your toes.
My apologies.
Ah, excellent.
I'm glad to find you all here.
Hey, Director Bear.
Boxo, Lamas, Hulamine, Mishra, We're
gearing up to hold a very important meeting.
in the Dead's Lament Stratum.
I'd love for you all to accompany me.
These humans, along with
the magical item Boxo,
are the survivors of a harrowing
encounter with the Netherlord.
The famous magical merchant box, huh?
The one that sells unusual items
at fair prices without the hassle?
Indeed.
Not to mention his useful
abilities that have
saved us from certain
death on many occasions.
He wasn't kidding.
This must be important if the directors
of each stratum's hunters association are
here Let's cut right to the chase the fell
netherlord who appeared a few days ago.
He is the demon Lord's left-armed
general I'm sure of it.
That spells big trouble the
netherlord that mysterious.
Fore-armed skeleton who made
a surprise appearance and an
unwelcome one when we defeated
the dead's lament stratum lord?
He stopped Hulamis and
Shuey's hearts using magic.
Luckily, I transformed into an AED,
and my electroshocks
successfully resuscitated them.
It's a miracle that nobody died, but we
can't let a bad dude like him run free.
That's Kerioyl, the leader
of the Menagerie of Fools.
I can't see his face, but he
seems more menacing than usual.
Question.
Sorry, but what is a left-armed general?
Far to the north, beyond
the reaches of this dungeon,
There lies a land ruled by the Demon Lord.
There's a Demon Lord?
Wait, I guess it would be kind of weird
not to have one in a world like this.
If you think of the Demon
Lord himself as the head,
then rank the others in descending order.
Right arm, left arm, then the right
leg, and the left leg as last.
So the left arm general would be the number
three rank in the Demon Lord's forces.
The number three rank, huh?
Why would a leader be
in a place like that?
The Demon Lord's forces
are never good news.
It seems unlikely that
they would invade us.
They would have to make it past
empires and fortified cities.
So, what do we do?
He attacked association members inside the
dungeon and our collective watch to boot.
That means we hit him with everything
we've got and show no mercy!
Whoa, you don't get this
riled up very often.
Letting him get away with this
would be bad for business.
And we've got some skilled
hunters who will help out.
The Origin Stratum will
provide some as well.
With what that bag of bones put my people
through, he's in for some serious payback.
I shall fight alongside you as well.
I, too, wish to settle the score.
You've got my fist, too.
After what he did to Hulemy and Shui, I
won't rest until I suck him real good.
That right, Boxo? Hello there.
And Hulemy, you can help us
figure out the plan of attack.
I'll help with planning, but
that bony jerk tried to kill me.
I can't wait to pay him back in person.
I like your style.
I appreciate all the enthusiasm.
The Clearblow-Legged Stratum will put
nothing but our best on this mission.
Let us all work together to bring down
the Netherlord once and for all! Yeah!
It's times like these
when I can't help but
miss having fists to
raise with my friends.
It wasn't long before the Aces from each
Stratum showed up to enlist in our cause.
Hi, Llamas, Hulemy, Boxo.
You two are in the Assault Squad?
Of course.
Hello there, Boxo.
Been wondering where my favorite
sentient snack dispenser went.
Let's see, I'll take the
usual Miss soup and a water.
I feel it.
Today's the day I get
lucky with those numbers.
The gate guards are one thing.
But why is the elderly couple I see
every morning part of the assault squad?
Hello, Boxo.
You too, llamas.
Oh, hi, director.
I heard you were there
when Shui needed you.
I'm so grateful.
Hoxie runs an orphanage
in the Origin Stratum.
I'm pretty sure she
taught Shui archery, too.
Hello, Hoxie.
Will you be joining us
on this mission, too?
Has life been treating you well?
Shimelai, Yumite.
Yes, I am, and it has.
They all know each other?
Well then, maybe I've
underestimated all three of them.
That day, ace hunters from each
stratum came rushing to our aid.
And we held a kickoff party before
setting out after the Netherlord.
So many different types of people.
That's right, and I bet every one of them
possesses some kind of powerful blessing.
What's with all the
old fogies around here?
This ain't no nursing home.
You geezers sure you're up to snuff?
Watch your mouth.
You know what happens to people
with no manners around here?
Nothing good.
What did you say?
Because it sounds like you're
trying to start something.
Do you know who we are?
Uh-oh. Hello there.
What's up?
Someone getting mouthy?
Hey, Lamas, give this guy a
little thump and knock him out.
Wait a sec.
Are you telling me you're with these guys?
Yeah, you bet I am.
Though I guess if you
want to get technical,
I'm still trying to get
them to join my group.
That's sweet, Captain Carry Oil.
You said Carry Oil?
You're not Captain Carry Oil
of the Menagerie of Fools?
And what if I am?
Nothing!
Nothing at all, Captain Carry Oil!
You said that was...
You heard it, folks.
I'm the leader of the Menagerie of Fools.
Name's Carry Oil.
And as my members are out of commission,
I am especially grateful for your help.
Oh, it's rare for the captain
to greet anyone so politely.
By the way,
Shui and the Red and White
Twins have yet to recover,
so they're apparently
sitting this one out.
Not that they wanted to
stay behind, of course.
My name is Mishuel.
I may be young and inexperienced,
but I so look forward to your
guidance and encouragement.
And my name is Hoxie.
I'm here from the Origin Strand.
Hello there, I'm Yumitei.
My blessings are a bit of healing light
along with a whole lot of swordsmanship.
The name's Shimei Lai.
I know magic and have several blessings.
Ask and I'll tell ya.
Once again, I am Karios.
And I'm Gorth.
I'm Hulemy, a magic item engineer
and Lamas' childhood friend.
That's me, Lamas!
And this here is my magical
partner, Boxo. Hello there!
Ah, a vanguard, mirror
guard, and recovery team.
That's a fairly well-balanced party,
although our older member's
strength has yet to be demonstrated.
I have faith in Captain Kerioyl.
I know he won't lead us astray.
Nice to meet you all.
Our search begins tomorrow.
Let's get sweet revenge
on that bonehead! Yeah!
Boxo! Boxo!
Boxo!
The following day,
we split into several teams and each group
headed towards their
intended search target.
I'm really sorry to saddle you
all with this dangerous task.
You never change, do you, Director Bear?
Your leadership style is as
self-deprecating as ever That's right,
everyone signed on willingly.
There's nothing to apologize for
Well, there's a sight
that brings back memories.
Up ahead, there's a group
of monsters lying in wait!
Hmm.
Yumite, Hoxie, why don't the
three of us go deal with them?
A group effort with my senior members?
The thought has me all nostalgic.
Oh, light and shroud my arrowheads.
I love when she shoots three at once.
My, expertly done.
Still fighting as dirty as ever.
That's our Hoxie.
Wow, I'm impressed.
Looks like those monsters are still so far
away that they haven't
even noticed us yet.
Time to invite them to the party!
Good show, you three.
It seems your skills are as sharp as ever.
Nah, we're not in top form anymore.
Soon, though, guess I had better
polish up my magic skills.
My cuts aren't as sharp as they once were.
If only Agent could spare warriors.
This battle is certainly not
one that I'd brag about to Shui,
but the next one sure will be.
So modest too, Boxo.
We're gonna have to work hard to keep up.
Hello there.
Dang, this hits the spot.
Shui would be so jealous if she knew.
I'd like to try every one of
his foods on this campaign.
If it meant eating his food for every
meal, would follow Boxxo to hell and back.
You said it!
Come back for as many helpings as
you want, if it'll keep morale high.
Here's a tip.
Lower your center of gravity.
That'll make things much easier and
it'll improve your power and accuracy.
My center of gravity?
Yeah, I'll try it.
That felt much better.
And it looked better, too.
Your work should be about getting used
to fighting without Boxo on your back.
Right!
Blessing of Might gives Lamas
more strength than she can handle.
She has to work hard
learning to control it.
Usually she has me on her back, which
gives her just the right handicap.
If she could manage her strength
well enough without me...
You can do it, Lamas!
Hey boxo you got a minute?
Hello there!
This one thing's been bothering
me it makes no sense but...
I think the nether lord
let llamas go on purpose.
Heal me!
If he had wiped us out in that moment,
we wouldn't have reported back or
met with the other stratum directors
which means this elite assault
force would never have been formed.
In other words what if his goal
is to use himself as bait to
gather as many ace hunters here
to this stratum as possible?
If you're right about that
then we really fell for it.
Anyway that's as far as i've
gotten with that theory though.
I know the worst case
scenario but i don't know
for sure so it's best
not to cause any alarm.
You're the only one I can tell, Boxo.
Hello there!
Huh?
Oh, thank you.
Don't mind if I do.
That's right.
Have a milk tea about it and relax.
We'll figure it out.
The flow of magic power seems odd.
It's increasing and
growing rather unsettled.
I have a feeling this
could spell trouble for us.
Turns out the old guy was right.
Not long after that conversation,
We discovered that another hunter
team had found the Netherlord.
Take this!
Good.
We're in position behind him.
Hoxie and Shimelai will
provide covering fire.
You bet we will.
Karyos and Gorth, you
two will stand guard.
Sign your orders, sir.
Lamas, we have tons of aces
out here. Don't go nuts.
I'll do my best.
Help us out, Boxo.
Hello there.
Everyone else will charge him.
While our goal is ultimately to slay the
Netherlord, do not do anything reckless.
We can buy time until
reinforcements arrive.
Kill me, sir.
Let's show them what the
dungeon's finest can do!
Hmph!
Form change!
Power lesser!
And with telekinesis,
the new blessing I acquired in that
last battle I've been training every
night to build up my physical strength
and dexterity let's see what I
can do with it now how do you monsters
feel about this huh I'm not technically
a vending machine anymore but what
else is new that was amazing boxo
Looks like we're just spinning our
wheels until we defeat the Netherlord.
Yes, indeed.
It seems he's using some
sort of regeneration spell.
Everyone, get away from there at once!
The Netherlord is gathering a vast
amount of magic power to himself.
I suspect it's some kind
of massive explosion spell.
Let's split right!
But what about the other team of hunters?
I'll take care of them.
I suggest you all cover your ears.
But I don't have hands!
Or ears.
Or eardrums, for that matter.
Major spell incoming!
Fall back!
Now why would they do that?
And was it in time?
Deploying barrier!
Well, well, well.
Not a single death, eh?
Elite hunters are not to be trifled with.
All my monsters perish, but so what?
I can always make all.
There's no way to beat him at this rate.
Only one of us has the power
to turn the tide of battle.
And that's me.
Ah, the blessing of my
girl and her magic item.
I'll be your worthy adversary
if you can reach me.
Okay.
It's now or never.
That's not the real me.
I'm far above the battlefield.
Lamas flung me up here during the
mayhem of that big explosion spell.
She's carrying a decoy,
a magic item Hulemy made.
The housing-only me.
The real me transformed.
Manipulated balloons using telekinesis and
is directly above the Netherlord's head.
Here goes...
Form change!
Japan's largest vending machine, which
can be found in a certain fishing harbor.
It's over 18 meters tall and
has even been featured on TV!
Here it is!
The Giant Ice Vending Machine!
Find all you want, hunters.
We shall see if you have
what it takes to reach me.
Me?
What is that?
A vending machine, punk! What else?
I came prepared in case I
couldn't crush you right away!
Before I took on this huge body,
I switched back to the regular vending
machine and got my secret weapon ready!
Because I increased my physical strength,
my maximum electroshock
is now off the charts!
Eat, Fools!
Ah! Ah!
Boxxo!
Are you okay?
Are you hurt?
No damage anywhere?
I'm fine, Lamas.
As you can see.
Heads up!
He's still alive!
This staff is precious, you see!
I cannot lose it.
Nevertheless, you managed
to defeat a part of me,
but it was merely my left arm transformed?
though that is worthy of praise indeed.
His left arm?
Is this a joke?
You may have defeated my appendage, but
I did still accomplish my original goal.
What was his original goal?
That was to gather all the capable
hunters here in one place. Shh!
Hume's hunch was right on.
You see, whenever hunters or
monsters perish within this dungeon,
the dungeon itself accumulates power.
in direct proportion to that of the dead.
Then I can employ said power
to produce more new monsters.
That is the way this dungeon operates.
Interesting.
Seems kind of similar to
the way I run on points.
From that knowledge, a brilliant
plan fomented in my mind.
I would kill everything
in this dungeon and
use the power to produce
a new pack of monsters.
Now then, perhaps the more astute among you
have already figured out what I'm doing.
I knew it.
If all the aces are gathered in
this place, then that means...
The other strata's defenses
are stretched thin.
If they were attacked...
It'd be real bad!
Now, given the current situation, don't
you think it'd be wise to hurry back?
You may transfer to other strata,
but I'll see to it that you
cannot leave the dungeon.
And so round two begins.
Struggle against me with all your might.
You will not thwart me.
Give your lives and
your power to my cause.
Oh
You could even win a reward.
I look forward to serving you again.